sense-lang.org 2017-06-08

# TERMS OF USE

29/2/16

**Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

Personal Information You Choose to Provide

Registration Information.

You will provide us information when you register to be a student/teacher of Sense-lang.org school platform or register for email newsletters and alerts. You may also provide additional comments on how you see Sense-lang.org servicing your needs and interests. 

Email Information.

Our report service delivery relies on the email address given by the teacher during registration.  
As part of the Premium Course product, typing Certificates are sent through email to the user according to the results achieved.   
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. 

Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site.  We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at senselang.support@gmail.com.

What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.  Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access or control over those cookies. 

How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

As you use our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

Google products and cookies

As you use our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other We are using google products which uses cookies. You can find more information about those cokkies under: <http://www.google.com/intl/iw/policies/privacy/partners/>

Notice of New Services and Changes

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at senselang.support@gmail.com.

How Do We Protect Your Information?

How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore as is the case with any organization - we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information . 

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us at senselang.support@gmail.com

 How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

Personal info can be easily modified using the option “Personal Info” on the menu available in the left side of the screen.

Certain Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interactions on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**  
Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
       **•**  On our Privacy Policy Page  
Users are able to change their personal information:  
       **•**  By logging in to their account

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**  
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**  
It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.  
We do not specifically market to children under 13. 

**What type of information is collected from the students?**  
1) First Name  
2) Last Name  
3) Email (optional)

According to COPPA regulation, schools are allowed to provide consent on behalf of the student parent. The school may consider providing parents with a notice of Sense-lang online service personal information collection.

**How does Sense-lang use this personal information?**  
The student personal information is essential to support internal operations and account personalization solely for the use and benefit of the school, and for no other commercial purpose.

**Does Sense-lang use or share personal information for commercial purposes not related to the provision of the online services requested by the school?   **  
No. The students personal information is stored solely for the use and benefit of the school.

**Does Sense-lang enable the school to review and delete the personal information collected from their students?**  
Yes. The teacher management tools allow the school to review, modify or delete the collected personal information.

**What measures does Sense-lang take to protect the security, confidentiality, and integrity of the collected personal information?  **  
We follow accepted industry standards to protect any provided personal information. Each student (and teacher) account has personalized credentials (unique username and password chosen by the school or student). The teacher account holds the credentials of all students' accounts. 

**What are Sense-lang data retention and deletion policies for children’s personal information?**

Student accounts can be removed only by the teacher. From time to time, Sense-lang reserves the right to remove teacher accounts (along with student accounts) with no activity for at least 6 months. 

**CONTACT US**

MINDKIT LTD is the operator of this Site and questions regarding this Privacy Policy and use of Personal Information should be directed to Sense-lang.org through any of the following methods:  
Mailing address: 41 Themistokli Dervi, Hawaii Nicosia Tower, Nicosia, Cyprus  
Email: senselang.support@gmail.com  
Phone: +1 (646) 517-3853

Note that the phone number is only for questions regarding this Privacy Policy.
